So, your promise.
Tell me about my sister.
She was in my class.
At the same school where
your teacher committed suicide?
No, a different one.
After that happened,
I was transferred to another school.
That was where I met Elena.
She was such a good person.
Transferring schools and my teacher's suicide
made me distance myself from others,
but she seemed determined
to strike up a conversation with me.
She helped me feel less alone,
even just a little.
I felt like I could really trust her.
I mean, I might have
had some ulterior motives...
Didn't need to know that...
That's why I find it difficult
to believe what you're saying.
Would Elena really kill her parents
and murder countless others?
Lame. Only 2,000 yen.
Do you think the person that
dropped this was looking for coins?
Get rid of it. Don't get distracted.
We're after bigger prey.
What?
Are you giving me orders? I'll kill you.
Stop, Subaru.
I'm tired. I'm going home.
Don't get upset with him. He's still a child.
I know.
We won't be able to complete
our goals without his help.
Not here. Let's keep on going.
Okay.
Hey, Shuichi.
You said there were dangerous people
in these mountains, right?
Have you ever run into one of them?
Yes.
So you have! What should we do
if we see one?! Please tell me!
To tell the truth, I haven't--
I killed her.
What?
On the day I first went to Clair's apartment,
some woman attacked us out of nowhere...
We fought, and...
It can't be true.
You... You wouldn't kill another person...
Oh, I get it! She did it, didn't she?
While she was inside you, like I am now!
No. I'm the one that killed her.
I didn't stop Clair.
And I knew what she was going to do.
What?
That smell...
She's not alone. There are two... Three!
I don't believe it!
Are these Clair's sister's friends?!
I can tell by the smell alone--
They are on a completely different level!
Their power... There's no way
we could match them!
My wallet's scent is coming from them?
What should we do? My ID is in there...
What if they come to my house?
Hey, Shuichi... They're not bad people, right?
This strength... They're her allies.
If we make one wrong move...
Hey, do you think I should
tell my parents to run away?
Am I overthinking it?
Let's go after them.
We can't do that! What if they find us?!
It's okay. I will save you.
Sorry, we had a lot to talk about.
But the pact is complete.
This girl... Clair is now one of us.
Glad to be a part of the team!
You finished the pact!
So we can talk to her now, right?
My name is Yota Murakami.
I'm 19, no real job yet.
I'm into music, and I'm looking for a girlfr--
Hey, where is Shuichi?
Your friend ran off somewhere
with Yoshioka--the girl with the helmet--
and they haven't come back.
Why? Do they know each other?
I don't think so.
My bad, I should have stopped them.
They said they'd be back soon,
that they were going on a walk.
--That stupid girl. Who cares about her? She's--
--Hey, you.
Do you know where Shuichi went?
That's crazy, you can record video.
You're like a real camera.
Convenient for a voyeur, eh?
Shut up! I'm just into making movies!
I followed them because--
I don't care why you did.
I just want to know where Shuichi is.
Show me the rest.
That's where I stopped recording.
I lost them after that.
I see.
Please excuse me,
I'm going to go look for Shuichi.
Hold on.
They're not back, and we haven't
heard from them for over an hour--
There's a good chance
they're in some kind of trouble.
Surely you realize that.
I don't care. It's not like
I'm going to bother you guys.
I thought you were a bit more well behaved...
Although I like that you
won't abandon your friend.
Let's give her an escort.
Not that we have a lot of
natural fighters in our group.
There is one though. Yota, do you mind?
Not at all.
What?
You're not just some ugly dude
that turns handsome?
Who are you calling ugly?!
Hey, she said--
I told you. We don't talk about our allies'
secrets to anyone who isn't an ally.
Anyhow, I'll leave it to you two.
This is our problem, too.
Yoshioka is one of us.
And of course, you are too.
It was the same then.
My weakness caused her death.
I was so scared.
Only worried about saving myself.
But I won't run away anymore!
No matter who I have to face!
No matter what happens!
The scents have split.
The one with the wallet is alone!
This might work out!
What might?
Do you want something?
A kid?! When did he--?!
Hey. You called me a kid, huh?
You trying to make fun of me?
Uh... I'm looking for my wallet...
You piss me off.
Little shits...
Wha--
Die.
No matter who I have to face.
No matter what happens.
I promised... I'd save you...
Father, Mother. That's enough.
Squashed!
Hey, you want to go out with me?
Fuck off.
You're totally my type, Clairy!
Don't call me that, creep. Fuck off.
Wait, is that really your actual face?
Why didn't you hide your face
when you first met us?
I don't have any reason to hide it.
I don't have family or anyone else
that I need to keep secrets from.
You seemed a bit timid when I first saw you.
I was just worried.
I'm the only one in
the group that can fight, right?
If something were to happen,
would I be able to protect them by myself?
Nope.
I know I don't look impressive,
but I'm pretty strong!
I still don't think so.
There are crazy monsters in these mountains,
things you can't even imagine.
You didn't have the same
fearsome scent that they did.
Scent, huh?
Okay, so why did you join
a team of weaklings like us?
Anyone would have been fine.
You happened to be the first ones I met.
I just wanted information.
I also thought it'd be easy
to use a bunch of clowns like you.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about!
You're so cool, totally my type!
Shut up. Fuck off.
Wait, so is that costume guy your boyfriend?
No.
Oh!
It's more than that. He's my other half.
Shuichi and I. We two are one.
Wait for me, Shuichi. I'll be there soon.
Little shits. Not even worth my time.
Hey, Shuichi.
Maybe the form you take means something.
It's frustrating.
Why are we so weak?
It frustrates you, too... Doesn't it?
What an incredible idea!
Letting someone inside of you
to make up for your own weakness.
What the hell is this?
What is it?
I'm worried about Subaru.
I'm going to go check on him.
I doubt there's anyone around
here that could harm him.
You're right. Still... He's only a kid.
What was that scream?
Let's go.
Seriously? How cool.
A metamorphosis, huh?
You're still shit to me.
Okay, fine.
I was bored anyway.
Let's have some fun.
Huh. Are you a rare, like me?
Still.
I bet I'm rarer than you.
The rage... It's welling up...
I've never been so angry about
something that was done to me.
Me?
Who am I?
Am I Shuichi Kagaya?
Am I Chihiro Yoshioka?
No. I am neither.
But I know everything about her.
Everything she's ever done.
What kind of person she was.
And that is why...
...he must pay!
He crushed her and threw her away,
like a worthless piece of trash...
And that is my rage!
Yoshioka feels it too.
He treated me like trash. And now we rage!
And now...
The rage will burn!
I want to kill this boy!
Die!
What...?
Stay out of this, Elena! He's--
Subaru. You have an important part to play.
I don't want you to use that power here.
Fine.
It's her.
She's the enemy.
She tried to kill Clair and I...
And she turned me into a monster!
I must stop her!
Do I know this person?
No...
Is this... Shuichi's memory?
I have to stop her...
I have to stop this vile woman!
Huh?
Why...?
Ow, ow!
Ah, I'm fine. Please don't be frightened.
Thank you.
You're the one who found this coin, aren't you?
There's someone I want to be with!
Ah, are you talking about... him?
Yes.
But even if I could be with him...
I could never... Not again... Not him...
So, this is the path you have chosen, huh?
A dream.
That's the first I've ever had.
Is it because of this body?
I wonder just how long it's been.
The seasons come and go.
Time goes ticking by,
and the world keeps changing.
It's truly fascinating. I feel like
I must watch where this all leads.
Do you know those guys?
No.
Not that I care. But you
better not get in my way again.
If you do... Nothing will stop me, not even you.
Fine. You're welcome to try.
Even if I'm killed...
...I won't be allowed to die
until this is all over. It won't happen.
I was out of line.
What is this?
What the hell happened here?
Hey, stop! We still don't know
if there are enemies out here!
Shuichi!
"Episode 8: Shadows in Memory"